<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en">
    <head>
      <meta charset="utf-8">
      <meta name="description" content="Basic HTML elements"/>
      <meta name="keywords" content="HTML5, tags"/>
      <meta name="author" content="Nicholas"/>
      <link href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css2?family=Open+Sans&display=swap" rel="stylesheet">
      <link rel="shortcut icon" href="css/img/fav-icon.jpg" type="image/jpg">
      <link rel="stylesheet" href="css/style.css">
      <title>UPDATES: Dota 2</title>
    </head>

<body id="bgimg4">
    <nav>
        <div class="logo">
            <h4><a href="./index.html"><img src="css/img/logo.png" alt="Logo"></a></h4>
        </div>
          <ul class="nav-links">
            <li><a href="./index.html">Main</a>
                <div class="sub-menu">
                    <ul>
                      <li><a href="./home.html">Home</a></li>
                      <li><a href="./characters.html">Heroes</a></li>
                      <li><a href="./updates.html" class="position">Updates</a></li>
                      <li><a href="./esports.html">Esports</a></li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
            </li>
            <li><a href="./aboutme.html">Profile</a></li>
            <li><a href="./enquiry.html">Enquiry</a></li>
            <li><a href="./disclaimer.html">Disclaimer</a></li>
            <li><a href="./acknowledgement.html">Acknowledgement</a></li>
            <li><a href="./enhancement.html">Enhancements</a></li>
          </ul>
    </nav>
<br>
<section class="section">
  <div class="content">
  <img src="css/img/upd1.jpg" alt="upd1" class="left">
  <h1 class="ti-title2">Spring Cleaning Update 2022</h1>
  <h2 class="ti-title3">Released date: 25 March 2022</h2>
    <p class="ti-p2">There's nothing creeps enjoy more than swapping out swords for brooms and sweeping up the barracks. Fortunately for us, that means it's time to enjoy the fruits of their janitorial efforts as today's patch opens the windows and doors of Dota for the Spring Cleaning Update for 2022 — focused on bug fixes and a passel of quality-of-life improvements.

You can head over to the Spring Cleaning Update page to peruse some featured highlights — like improvements to Aghanim's tooltips, Muting Controls, Shop Searches, and Demo Hero mode —  or dig into the full list of changes.

Plus, don't miss all the other springtime action unfolding as the DPC Tour continues the march towards the next Major. Tune in daily for high-level Dota that showcases established powerhouses along with future stars competing around the globe.</p>
</div>
<br>
<div class="content">
  <img src="css/img/upd2.jpg" alt="upd2" class="right">
  <h1 class="ti-title2">DPC Spring Tour & Fantasy Kickoff</h1>
  <h2 class="ti-title3">Released date: 12 March 2022</h2>
    <p class="ti-p2">The brief interlude following last season's Regional Finals introduced both Primal Beast and the 7.31 Gameplay update to the world, and while players are still exploring the new-meta landscape, it's time for Dota's top talent to face off and show the rest of us how it's truly done.

Tune in as the DPC Spring Tour kicks off on March 14, sparking action across the globe as teams battle through Regional Leagues to earn their spot in the Spring Major. All are eager to reach the next leg of the Tour on a high note, with budding dreams of qualifying for The International, which looms further beyond.

Fantasy for the DPC Spring Tour is now available, ready to help plug you directly into the pro scene from the Spring Tour's very first game. Featuring a new distribution of rewards, this season guarantees you’ll haul something home just by playing — so open your first card packs today and set to planning your preferred regional rosters in preparation for next week's start of play.</p>
</div>
<br>
<div class="content">
  <img src="css/img/upd3.jpg" alt="upd3" class="left">
  <h1 class="ti-title2">Dota Plus Update — Spring 2022</h1>
  <h2 class="ti-title3">Released date: 2 March 2022</h2>
    <p class="ti-p2">As spring winds arrive to help break winter's final grip, it's time to welcome a new seasonal Dota Plus update — ushering with it new Plus features arriving from the latest Battle Pass, updated seasonal quests and guild rewards, and an all-new treasure to explore.

Assistant Features
Joining stack and pull timers, Dota Plus now includes a Rune Spawn Indicator, which you can see when pressing Alt. In addition, the Plus Neutral Item Upgrade Recommendations have also been promoted to a core Plus feature, helping you keep track of neutral items in your team's stash that might better fit your hero than your current choice.

Dota Plus Seasonal Treasure
The Spring 2022 Seasonal Treasure is here and available for purchase with shards. Exclusive to Dota Plus members, this treasure features all new sets for Axe, Omniknight, Lion, Anti-Mage, Grimstroke, Kunkka, Death Prophet, and Winter Wyvern. There's also a chance to unlock Leafy the Seadragon courier, who swims in bearing random prismatic and kinetic gems.

Updated Seasonal Quests & Guild Rewards
Today’s update also comes with a new set of Dota Plus quests to shore up your shard stash for new relics and the Seasonal Treasure — offering up to 115,200 shards over the course of the season. Guild rewards have also been updated, making new emoticons, sprays, and chat wheels available to high-scoring guilds.</p>
</div>
<br>
<div class="content">
  <img src="css/img/upd4.jpg" alt="upd4" class="right">
  <h1 class="ti-title2">7.31b Gameplay Update</h1>
  <h2 class="ti-title3">Released date: 1 March 2022</h2>
  <p class="ti-p2">Cooldown reduction now stacks diminishingly
Moved the Bounty Runes from the triangle to the primary jungle
Moved the Dire and Radiant offlane towers 320 units further away from base
When a hero respawns in the fountain, they are inveulnerable as long as there's at least one enemy hero in the base until they issue a command
Kill gold information now shows a breakdown of gold bounty for the killer plus proximity gold
The following abilities now consistently reveal invisibility for their duration:  Winter's Curse,  Aether Remnant,  Berserker's Rage (Ensnare),  Shackles,  Life Drain,  Dismember,  Fortune's End,  Sinister Gaze,  Searing Chains,  Enchant Remnant, Rod of Atos icon.png Rod of Atos, Gleipnir icon.png Gleipnir,  Ensnare
Attack and armor types are now represented through abilities. Most damage remains unchanged with a few exceptions in creep vs creep and creep vs tower situations
Added new ability:  Piercing. Piercing units deal 150% bonus damage to non-hero units and 50% less damage to Standard Units
Added new ability:  Reinforced. Reinforced units deal 150% bonus damage to other Reinforced units and reduce damage received from heroes by 50% and from non-hero units by 30%
Added new ability:  Runty. Runty units deal 25% less damage to heroes
Piercing, Reinforced, and Runty aren't stealable (e.g: Devour)
Ranged creeps and their upgrades all have the  Piercing ability.
</p>
</div>
</section>



<div class="footer">
    Copyright 2014 Sea Monsters Inc. All Right Reserved.
</div>

</body>
</html>
